本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
拒不退款
旅行者  你好
Well, hello there, traveler.
我瞧见你的车在这偏僻的乡村小路上抛锚了
I see your car broke down on this lonesome country road,
这里人迹稀少  没人能听见你的尖叫
a place so remote that no one can hear your screams!
就当我没说过
Pretend I didn't say that.
进来  快进来  但要当心
Come in, come in, but be warned,
如果你进来了  可能会沉迷于我的故事
if you enter you may be subjected to my tales.
我为了卖出商品而编造的故事
Tales designed to sell my merchandise!
抱歉  我刚刚在想先前听到的一些有趣的事
Sorry, I was thinking of something funny I heard earlier.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
时间轴： moonywen
翻译： 阿拱  volin1443  baker
■
校订： Enpistu  moonywen  WaitinZ
后期： moonywen  WaitinZ
怪诞小镇  第二季第六集
Gravity Falls  S02E06  Little Gift Shop of Horrors
你已经来到闭馆后的神秘小屋
You've come to the Mystery Shack after-hours,
现在只有最恐怖的
a time when only our creepiest
和被诅咒的物品出售
and most cursed objects are for sale,
就像那边的东西一样
like that thing there!
不喜欢吗  身上洞太多吗
No, not a fan? Too many orifices?
好吧  我可以看出你在寻找的是
All right, I can tell what you're looking for
这只假手
is this disembodied hand.
为什么这么贵
Why is it so expensive?
这事说来话长了
Well, that's quite a tale
这个叫做断手
and it's called Hands Off!
不  说真的  这个断手是不卖的
No, seriously, hands off, that's not for sale.
好吧
All right.
断手
Hands Off!
重力泉跳蚤市场
当停车场遇上垃圾堆
跳蚤市场  交换旧货  交换旧货
Swap meet! Swap meet! Swap meet!
看看这些无价之宝
Look at all these priceless treasures.
摇头娃娃
Bobbly-heads!
我说什么他们都同意呢
They agree with everything I say.
教授眼镜
Professor glasses!
戴上它我看起来就像个天才
They make me look like a genius.
瞧瞧这些假黄金做的美物
Look at these faux-gold beauties.
真有黑帮老大的范儿啊
They're mob-boss quality.
好啦  孩子们  准备看我一展讨价议价的美妙艺术吧
All right, kids, prepare to watch the delicate art of the deal.
喂  妖婆  这些旧表多少钱
Hey, hag-face! How much for the junk watches?
这些表不卖
They are not for sale.
就是不卖给你  斯坦・派恩斯
Not for you, Stan Pines!
风在轻吟你的名字
The wind whispers your name!
嘘  你们都安静点
Shh... Shush, you guys.
够了  我懂了  你这个怪人
All right, I get it, you're creepy.
总之  你少说几句就能多卖几块手表
Anyway, less talky, more watchy!
别碰我的手表
Get your hands off my watch!
恶心  怪人
Yeesh! Freak show.
哇  某人得练练社交技巧喽
Wow, someone needs to work on their social skills.
还有观察能力
And their observation skills.
砰
Boom!
干的好  能偷天盗影的手
Good job, heisting hands.
斯坦叔公  你真要从女巫那儿偷东西吗
Grunkle Stan, are you seriously shoplifting from a witch?
这样听来好像个诅咒
That sounded like a curse.
"That sounded like a curse!"
嘿  有人想买条湿毛毯吗
Hey, anyone want to buy a wet blanket?
我们出售湿毛毯呢
We got a wet blanket for sale!
湿毛巾
我在这市场上混不下去了
I can't survive in this market.
呵呵  诅咒
Ha, curse.
是啊
Yeah, right.
等等  这个诅咒是恶毒的还是一般毒
Wait, is this curse ugly or normal ugly?
貌似我一点事都没有
Looks like I got off scot-free.
好了  小家伙们  早饭时间
All right, kiddos, breakfast time.
准备享受这盘
Prepare your mouths for--
啊  天哪  没有手
Whoa! Whoa-ah! No hands!
斯坦叔公  你的手怎么啦
Grunkle Stan, what happened to your hands?
我大概是中了点诅咒吧
So I might have got cursed a little,
不过这表看起来真棒  是吧
but the watch looks nice, right?
蠢货  偷窃的双手会揭发邪恶的面孔
Foolish man, thieving hands find wicked face!
你必须归还不属于你的东西
You must return what isn't yours...
这样好多了
That's better.
我跟你说过  斯坦叔公
I told you, Grunkle Stan,
你必须把表还回去并且道歉
you got to give that watch back and apologize.
什么
What?
应该是那个老太婆给我道歉才对
That old crone should apologize to me
因为她剥夺了我买便宜货的权力
for denying my right to buy cheap junk.
我才不需要手呢  我可是有自尊的人
I don't need hands, I've got self respect.
梅宝  亲爱的  你能帮你叔公做双手吗
Mabel, sweetie, will you make your uncle some hands?
啦啦啦  双手大改造
La-la-la. Hands makeover!
和你的“新手”打个招呼吧  加引号
Say hello to your "New hands"! In quotes.
做的不错  孩子
Nice work, kid.
瞧  新手比预想好多了
See, hands are overrated.
我准备好迎接这一天啦
I'm ready to take on the day!
夫人
Ma'am.
派恩斯先生
Hey, Mr. Pines.
我们是不是该像平常一样玩扔鸡蛋游戏了
Should we play toss me a dozen eggs like we always do?
不  吉米  等等  今天不行
No, Jimmy, wait! Not today!
今天不行
Not today!
我们去找那个巫婆吧
Let's find that witch.
跳蚤市场宣传册上说
According to the swap meet pamphlet,
手巫婆住在手巫婆山上的
the hand witch lives in a horrible hand witch lair
一个恐怖的手巫婆洞穴里
on Hand Witch Mountain.
别再说手巫婆了
Stop saying hand witch!
斯坦叔公  你刚才是不是拍了下我的肩膀
Grunkle Stan, did you just tap my shoulder?
孩子  我现在可什么都拍不了
Kid, I can't tap anything.
伙计们  你们能不要拍我两个肩膀了好吗
Guys, can you stop tapping both my shoulders?
手  好多手
Hands! Lots of hands!
看看这感人的一幕
Look at this touching scene.
击个掌
Up top!
你们真懂我
You guys, you guys get me.
行了  你个可怕的老姑娘  你抓住我了
All right, you horrible wench, you got me.
偷窃是错误的行为  等等  拿去
Stealing is wrong, etcetera, take it.
那现在能把我的手还给我吗
Now can I have my hands back?
有个手势我想与你分享
I have a certain gesture I'd like to share with you.
哎呀  拿回你的手可没那么简单
Alas, your hands cannot be gotten so easily.
咒语规定  呃
The spirits say, um...
只有一个吻才能解开这个诅咒
that the curse can only be broken by a kiss!
什么
What?
只能这样了  孩子们
It's all right, kids.
你们转过去
Just look away.
是亲嘴
A kiss on the lips!
天啊  休想  我才不会亲那个恶心的东西
What? Forget it! I'm not kissing any of that mess.
我还没那么需要我的手
I don't need my hands that bad.
是啊  你根本是在胡扯
Yeah, you're just making stuff up now.
孩子们  我们走
Let's go, kids.
不  等等  别走
No, wait! Don't go!
你是对的  你是对的
You're right, you're right.
刚才那些都是我编的
I was just making all that stuff up.
我就是想找人发展一下  你懂的
Just trying to get something going, you know.
最近难得结识其他人
So hard to meet people these days.
那么所有的这一切是就是为了能约个会
So this was all just a ploy to get a date?
我很饥渴  行了吧
I'm desperate, okay?
可每次我把人带到这里来
But every time I bring someone back here
如果没扣下他们的手  他们就会跑掉
without keeping their hands hostage, they just run away!
是啊  看看这可怕的地方
Well, yeah, look at this horror show.
对一个山洞来说也是够毛骨悚然的了
It's creepy even for a cave!
你只是需要重新装饰一下
You just need to redecorate.
比如说
For example...
一个手制烛台
A handelabra!
噢  手巫婆很喜欢这个
Ooh, the hand witch likes.
那就看我的吧
Then watch me work.
家居大改造
Home makeover!
迪普：油漆顾问
重新装修
Redecorate.
梅宝：上色
重新刷墙
Redo you.
斯坦：订锤子
改变环境
Change it around.
付出努力才能得到回报
You got to do it to make it work.
好了  现在看看你漂亮的新家吧
Okay. Time to take a look at your fantastic new cave.
男人们现在绝对能容忍你了
Men will definitely tolerate you now.
我还在茶几上给你留了本搭讪攻略
And I left a book of pickup lines on the end table.
噢  我的老天
Blah! Oh, my goodness!
不敢相信这还是原来那个山洞
I can't believe this is the same cave!
天哪
Oh, my goodness!
我高兴得说不出话来啦
I just can't find the words.
说句“把手还给你”怎么样
How about "Here's your hands back"?
噢  对了
Oh, right.
有点抖  有点痒
Shaky, Scratchy.
我想死你们这双坏家伙了
I've missed you old rascals.
你没问题了  姐们儿
You're all right, sister.
那你现在能做我的男朋友了吗
Will you be my boyfriend now?
不  没戏
No, never.
好吧  我什么也没学到
Well, I learned nothing.
又要回到我一瘸一拐的孤独生活了
Back to my crippling loneliness.
嗨  我在这片山区迷路了
Hey, I'm lost in these mountains.
我能在这里住一夜吗
Could I crash here for the night?
请进来吧
Please, come in. Uh...
搭讪攻略
“天哪  这是条太空裤吗”
"Girl, are those space pants?
“因为你的屁股举世无双啊”
Because your butt looks out of this world."
谢谢你注意到了
Well, thanks for noticing.
太好了
Yes!
好了  我懂了
All right, I get it.
你不想要手  你是个明智的顾客
You don't want the hand, you're a savvy customer.
但也许你会想买  呃
But perhaps you'd be interested in buying, um...
这只魔力猪
this magic pig.
他的确看起来没什么魔力
Sure he doesn't look magic,
但是我马上就能给他编一个
but there is a very interesting story
非常有意思的故事给你听
I'm about to make up about him,
故事的名字叫做
and it's called
怪猪奇谈
Abaconings!
怪猪                  奇谈
“搞毛啊多面体”
"The What-The-Heck-A-Hedron!
只要解开这个智力谜题
Solve this test of intelligence
你的照片就可能出现在这个盒子上
and your photo could be on this box."
这种虚假广告我还是能识破的
Whoa. That's false advertising I can get behind.
拜托
Come on.
那可是太遗憾了
Ooh, that's a bummer.
这是小梅梅与哼唧的早间广播
This is May May and The Hogg coming at you on the AM.
不知道咱在电台上能不能说这个哟
Not sure we can say that on the air.
别碰调频板了  老司机们
Don't touch that dial, truckers,
因为哼唧刚刚把它们都吃了
'cause The Hogg just ate it.
梅宝  你能消停会儿吗
Mabel, could you knock it off?
我正忙着解开这个智力游戏呢
I'm trying to solve this intelligence puzzle,
但似乎不太好弄啊
but it seems impossible.
也许你就是不够聪明呗
Maybe you're just not smart enough.
那我们走着瞧
We'll see about that.
传说中的洞察蘑菇就长在瀑布边上
Buried near the falls is the legendary percepshroom.
需要增强脑力时  将其碾碎
To increase brain power, grind it up
并在夜间涂抹于前额上
and apply to the forehead overnight.
明天  我就搞定你
Tomorrow, I own you!
我已经感觉到自己智商爆表了
I feel smarter already.
圆周率是3.1
The digits of pi are 3.1...
415926等等
415926 etcetera.
什么  谁说的
What? Who said that?
梅宝
Mabel?
迪普  快看
Whoa! Dipper, look.
朋友们早上好  是我呀  小猪摇摇
Greetings, friends. It is I, Waddles the pig.
什么
What?
摇摇  你怎么了
Waddles, what happened to you?
你是被学霸的灵魂附体了吗
Have you been possessed by the spirit of a nerd?
你们对我变化的不适是可以理解的
I understand my transformation may be vexing,
不过我已经准备了一个演示文稿
but I have prepared a presentation.
见笑了  我的猪蹄除了可爱别无它用
Forgive me. My pig arms are cute and useless.
健脑浆  你是吃了它以后造的这些吗
The brain goop! You ate it and built all this, didn't you?
这不科学
This isn't right!
小猪噜噜叫  小猪噜噜叫呀
The pig goes oink. The pig goes oink!
现在小猪可以叫出任何声音
Now the pig goes wherever he can shine
并用智慧之光将愚昧驱赶
the light of knowledge into the darkness of ignorance.
天哪 “搞毛啊多面体”
Whoa! What-the-heck-a-hedron!
你是怎么做到的
How did you do that?
我能教你的  迪普  我能教你很多东西
I can teach you, Dipper. I can teach you many things.
从天体物理学的奥秘到
From the secrets of astrophysics to the--
我真是爱死这个新的摇摇了
Man, I am loving this new Waddles.
是啊  他  他的确是变了
Yeah, he's, uh, he's definitely... different.
哥们儿  这个火箭小车真是太酷了
Dude, that rocket cart is amazing!
我们应该一起发明些什么
You and me should go invent stuff.
摇摇  你不想和我一起在楼上
Uh, Waddles, don't you want to stay up here
录些早间整人片段了吗
and record some morning pranks with me?
梅宝  这只猪才华横溢
Mabel, this pig's got a gift.
它需要和世界分享自己的才华
He needs to share it with the world.
对不起  梅宝
I'm sorry, Mabel.
生命中还有很多事情比发出屁声
There is more to life than making fart noises
和嘲笑屁声更加重要
and laughing at those fart noises.
我现在明白了
I see that now.
好  你们就抛下我一起玩耍吧
Yeah, you guys just go on without me.
噢  我的风筝挂在树上了
Oh, my kite got stuck in a tree.
我恨一切
I hate everything!
说不定我们可以帮上忙
I bet we could be of service.
对大自然的公然冒犯呀
Ah! An affront against nature!
别在意风筝了
Ha! Forget kites.
来  拿着这个我发明的火箭背包
Here, take this rocket pack I invented
亲身体验天堂吧
and explore the heavens yourself.
管他呢  格兰达要透过天窗观赏小帅哥了
Forget that, Grenda is gonna look at cute boys through skylights.
天高任我飞
I rule the sky!
哥们儿  我们做的那个火箭背包真是太帅了
Dude, that rocket pack we made was amazing.
别忘了我们为糖糖发明的激光枪
Don't forget the laser gun we made for Candy.
敌人吃我一枪
That's to my enemies!
欢迎收听小梅梅和哼唧的早间广播
Welcome to May May and The Hogg AM.
今日头条
Top story today,
处理我失去搭档后的绝望孤独
coping with crippling loneliness after losing my co-host.
孤独
Loneliness!
那碗粘糊糊的浆到底对你做了什么
What did that nasty goop do to you?
你这样并没有更加快乐吧  有吗
You're not happier like this, are you?
这是你目前最伟大的发明了
Ha-ha. This is your greatest invention yet.
它能解决人类的一切问题
It could solve every problem of mankind.
然后给我很多土豆  美味的土豆
And bring me many potatoes, delicious potatoes.
猪猪吃香香
Yummy yummy for my fat little pig tummy.
你们在这里干什么呢
What the heck is going on here?
梅宝  你刚好有幸见证我们最伟大的发明
Mabel, you are just in time to behold our greatest achievement.
“智粒子加速器”
The smarticle accelerator!
解开那个智力游戏只是冰山一角
Solving that brain puzzle was just the tip of the iceberg.
有了它  摇摇就能解决
With this, Waddles will be able to solve
宇宙间所有的极难谜题
all the greatest puzzles of the universe.
生命的起源  存在的意义
The origin of life. The meaning of existence.
男人为什么长乳头
Why dudes have nipples.
不久你的猪将闻名世界
Soon your pig is gonna be world famous,
与科学家和总统当面会谈
meeting with scientists, presidents.
我想试试能不能教它穿裤子
I wonder if I can teach him to wear pants.
全世界
The whole world?
那咱们还能在一起玩吗
But when will you have time for us?
我是你最好的朋友啊
I'm your best friend.
我依然是你的朋友  梅宝
I'm still your friend, Mabel.
但是我现在可以帮助人类了
But I'm helping people now.
那你能不能帮助我呢
But what about helping me?
你真的想把一生都花在
Do you really want to spend your whole life in meetings
和蠢了吧唧的天才会面上吗
with dumb smart guys?
那个垃圾脑浆已经让你忘记自己了
This brain junk has made you forget who you are.
还记得我们在一起的时光吗
Don't you remember us?
回忆那些时光
Remember those times
不要忘了回忆那些时光
Don't forget to remember those times
请记住要回忆那些时光
Just remember to remember those times
说得非常有道理
It all makes sense now.
如果我不能让自己最喜欢的人快乐
What good is helping the world
帮助整个世界又有什么意义
if I can't help my favorite person in the world?
好在我也造了个变笨装置
It's a good thing I built in a dum-dum switch.
智力增强
向前
倒退
摇摇  摇摇  不要啊  等一下
Waddles! Waddles, don't! Wait!
智力等级
高
低
猪
抱歉  迪普
I'm sorry, Dipper.
在我意识尚存的最后的八秒里
In my last eight seconds of consciousness,
我想告诉你
I want you to know
科学应该是追逐的目标
that science is a horizon to search for,
而不是握在手头的奖项
not a prize to hold in your hand.
而且我好想念被人挠肚子呀
Also I miss getting my tummy tickled.
噢  摇摇
Oh, Waddles.
不  我们的发明
No! Our invention!
我知道什么能让你开心起来
I know what will make you feel better.
一只简单小猪的简单拥抱
A simple hug from a simple pig.
大概吧
Yeah, guess so.
乖猪猪
Good pig.
知道吗  你是对的  别买猪了
You know what? You're right. Don't buy the pig.
其实我最好还是把它留给侄孙子侄孙女们
In fact I'm better off leaving it with my niece.
别在家里打枪  宝贝
No shooting in the house, sweetie.
但  也许别的东西会引起你的兴趣的
But perhaps I could interest you in something else.
像这些恐怖电影
Like these spooky movies!
电影什么的最棒了
Movies are great.
你们看着电影  吓坏了小女孩
You watch the movie, you scare the girl,
小女孩渐渐向你靠近
the girl snuggles up next to you.
接下来会发生什么  你懂的
Next thing you know,
你就得带娃  紧接着你的生活就会毁于一旦
you got to raise a kid, your life falls apart.
算了  忘了我最后说的吧
Forget that last part.
下一个故事就叫做  斗战粘土记
This next tale is called Clay Day!
斗战粘土记
你搞定了  闪闪甜心侠
You did it, Shimmery Twinkleheart!
不  是你搞定的哦
No, you did it, Cinnamon.
因为你相信自己能做到的
Because you believed in yourself.
看完了真是整个人都不好了
Everything about this is bad.
看完这个又浪费了我九十分钟的生命
Well, that just put me 90 minutes closer to death.
是时候让你们这些熊孩子看看我们那时的经典了
It's time you kids learn to watch the classics from my day.
爷爷级别的电影啊
Ooh, old people movies.
准备好看一些我们搞不清情节
Get ready for references we don't understand
道不明台词的老玩意儿吧
and words we can't repeat.
罗恩克劳塞克利历险记
和罗恩克劳塞克利作对是没有好下场的
You're no match for Loinclothiclese.
我是为了金裤子而战
I've come for the golden pants.
噢不  梅宝
Oh, no! Mabel!
嗯  看起来你姐姐崩溃了
Well, your sister is broken.
噢  斯坦叔公  我早该告诉你的
Oh, Grunkle Stan, I should have told you before
梅宝对老式定格动画
that Mabel has a childhood terror
有很大的童年阴影
of old-timey stop-motion animation.
我们小时候  这大概是她最大的恐惧了
It's like her number one fear since we were kids.
得了吧  那些假假的老电影能把她吓成什么样
Come on, those hokey old things, how scared could she be?
那个独眼巨人  他的脸简直就是噩梦
The Cyclops! His face is made of nightmares!
孩子  那只是部电影罢了  它伤不到你的
Kid, it's just a movie. It can't hurt you.
不许说话
No talking.
他们就是在等着你开口然后爬进你的嘴里的
They wait for you to talk and then crawl inside your mouth!
你干嘛要给她看那部电影啊
Why did you have to show her that tape?
总有办法让她克服这个恐惧的
There's got to be a way to get her over this!
动画大师  快乐的克莱莫
拍摄于俄勒冈州重力泉
嗯
Huh...
好吧  如果我们能让导演给梅宝展示
All right, if we can just get the director to show her
那些道具是假的  或许她就能冷静下来了
the models are fake, maybe she'll finally calm down.
这可不能确定啊  老兄  根据网络记载
I don't know, dude. According to the internet,
特效大师哈利・克莱莫神秘失踪了
special effects genius Harry Claymore is some kind of recluse.
他想要点私人空间  这我懂的
Man wants his privacy. I can respect that.
好了  所有人都翻过栅栏吧
Well, everyone over the fence.
看见没  梅宝  那些妖怪只是小小的粘土人偶
You see, Mabel, those monsters are just tiny clay figures
被某个社交无能的宅人摆出各种姿势  逐格拍摄下来
moved around one frame at a time by an antisocial shut-in.
那种人被称作动画师
Those people are called animators.
有人吗
Hello?
克莱莫先生在吗
Mr. Claymore?
我们想来看看你的模型
We want to get a look at your figurines.
我们不是狗仔队哦
We're not paparazzi.
看见没  梅宝  都是特效做出来的
See, Mabel, it's all just special effects.
你可以出来喽
You can come out.
才不
No!
孩子  听我说
Kid, listen to me.
最后一遍  根本没有必要去怕什么
For the last time, there is nothing here to be afraid of--
是独眼怪
It's slowly...
在慢慢挥掌打我们
swiping at us!
咱们静止不动就没事了
Let's escape by standing still!
噢  根本不管用啊
Oh, it didn't work!
怎么可能会发生这样的事  他们想要什么
How is this happening? What do they want?
恐怕他们想要你们吧
I'm afraid they want you.
哈利・克莱莫  特效大师  大约在上世纪七十年代吧
Harry Claymore, master of special effects, circa 1970 something.
哎呀  我的特效比你知道的还特别啊
Alas, my effects are more special than you know.
什么  这些怎么会是真的
What? But how are these things real?
-那定格动画呢  -什么
- What about stop motion? - What?
你真的相信有人
Do you really believe someone
会给他们逐格逐格地摆姿势照像吗
moves these figures one frame at a time?
我又不是受虐狂
I'm not a masochist.
我用暗黑魔法使他们自己动起来啊
I used black magic to make them animate themselves.
刚开始还挺好的  但是有一天
It was great at first, but one day...
重力泉八卦报
计算机动画发明
定格动画已死
看起来太真实
不要
No!
动画之魂在哪里
Where's the heart?!
然后他们都失业了
Now that they were out of work,
他们很生气  于是囚役了我
they went mad and enslaved me!
现在他们要把你们也变成邪恶的粘土野兽
And now they will turn you into unholy beasts of clay
加入他们的邪恶队伍
to join in their mischief!
这个嘛  派恩斯先生  至少你终于可以
Well, Mr. Pines, at least you'll finally
和你最喜欢的导演一起工作了
get to work with your favorite director.
关于工作二字  其实我想说的是  被困在那一大坨泥巴里
And by work, I mean, suffocate inside a big wad of clay.
救命啊
Help!
-谁来救救我们啊  -救命啊
- Somebody help us! - Help!
我该做些什么呢
Oh, what do I do?
我怎么可能打得过那些恶棍啊
How can I defeat those monstrosities?
嘿  我把它改成了我喜欢的样子耶
Hey, I changed it into something I like.
哇  我有主意了
Whoa, I think I have an idea!
嘿  独眼仔
Hey, one-eyed-clops!
对  就是跟你说话呢  大傻瓜
Yeah, I'm talking to you, dum-dum!
来抓我啊
Come at me!
抹去你的大脸
Wipe that face off your face.
噢  现在我可要对你大改造了
Oh, I've got big plans for you!
嘿  骷髅大傻瓜们
Hey, skeleton dorks!
现在是复仇时刻
It's "Clayback" Time!
梅宝  你战胜了自己的恐惧耶
Dude, you conquered your fear.
那是当然  因为她相信她自己
That's right. Because she believed in herself.
得了吧  闪闪甜心侠
Can it, Twinkleheart!
赶快开始击垮那些骷髅兵
Just start pounding those skeletons!
梅宝  你做到了
Mabel, you did it!
这么说你不再害怕了
So you're not scared anymore?
我现在可比以前还害怕  但是现在的恐惧是理性的
Oh, I'm scared twice as much now, but now I know it's rational.
孩子  我很抱歉怀疑了你  你是对的
Kid, I'm sorry I doubted you. You were right.
定格动画是真正的恶魔
Stop motion is pure evil.
而且大概还很烧钱
And probably really expensive.
相当烧钱
Incredibly expensive.
不管怎么说  这还是一场了不起的战斗
This is an impressive fight though.
我很庆幸我正面面对了它
I'm glad I'm facing towards it.
这是最爽的部分了
That was the best part.
罗恩克劳塞克利
与头多得不像话的生物
我想今天我们学会了如何重塑你的恐惧
Well, I think today we learned that you can remold your fears.
我只是很庆幸咱们没人变成粘土一块
I'm just glad none of us got turned into clay.
我的老天爷
Holy Toledo!
谁想看我变成任何东西
Who wants to see me change into most anything?
我都可以穿墙诶  哇哦
I can walk through walls. Whoa!
我们安全了  孩子们  我们安全了
We're safe now, kids. We're safe.
我就是搞不明白  你不想要猪
I don't get it. You don't want the pig,
你也不想要我的影碟  你到底想买些什么
you don't want my tapes... What are you gonna buy?!
这些美味的魔药怎么样
How about this delicious potion?
给  免费试喝哦
Here, have a free sample.
你真应该在你还有机会的时候
You should have bought my merch
买我的商品知道吗  哥们儿
when you had the chance, buddy.
但也没事
But that's OK.
我很快会有新东西上架哦
I'll have some new for sale very soon...
而这就是我们最新的展品
And here we have our latest attraction:
传奇性吝啬鬼
The legendary Cheapskate!
我看到它眨眼了耶
I saw it blinking.
哈  只是幻觉罢了
Ha! Just an optical illusion.
来这边  各位  跟紧点
Come along, everyone. Step right up!
没错  我是个混蛋
That's right, I'm a jerk.
嘿  想玩井字棋吗
Hey! Wanna play Tic-tac-toe?
嘿  我想当叉  让我当叉嘛
Hey! I wanted to be X's! Let me be X's.
相信我  你就让她当叉吧
Trust me, just let her be X's.
事实上  抱歉啦  我改主意啦
Actually, I'm sorry. I changed my mind.
我来当圈吧
I'll be O's.
好吧  估计你现在开始恨我了
OK, you're gonna hate me right now...
但  我还能当叉嘛
But is X's still a possibility?
救救我
我觉得你不会玩这个游戏耶
I don't think you're playing this right...